Hello?
Is this Baek Sun-ju of MBS?
Yes, this is she. May I help you?
Hello?
I'd like to request an interview.
What is this concerning?
I killed 11 people.
What do you mean?
Could you repeat that?
I am...
a serial killer.
SKULL CAVED IN BY BLUNT OBJECT
APPEARS TO BE HIGHLY INTERESTED
IN THE ACT OF KILLING ITSELF
PREMEDITATED RETALIATORY HOMICIDE
WEAPON OF CHOICE IS A SERRATED KNIFE
CAUSE OF DEATH IS DETERMINED
TO BE CYANIDE POISONING
MURDER REPORT
A heavy rain advisory has been
issued for Seoul this afternoon,
with expected rainfall
exceeding 100 mm per hour.
Be prepared for potential damage,
as the rain may be accompanied by
strong winds...
I don't like the sound of that.
What?
I think it'll rain a lot.
Ye-rin didn't take an umbrella.
Are you serious?
She'll buy one. She's old enough.
Is something bothering you?
It's just that...
she's been weird lately.
How so?
She doesn't talk and she looks gloomy.
Yeah?
I was suspicious so I checked
her bag a few days ago.
I found a razor blade.
A razor blade?
Yeah.
If it bothers you so much,
should I talk to her?
Could you?
Yeah, she's more open with you.
I think that's a good idea.
All right.
You really are something.
Thinking about her right now?
He said he killed 11 people.
Aren't you even scared?
I am.
I'm scared that a lunatic
gave me a false tip.
I know.
Aren't you overreacting
to a lunatic's bluff?
It's not too late.
I can still report to the HQ.
I'll arrest him and confirm
whether he's telling the truth...
And if it's the truth?
You think my company
will give me this story?
Don't you know
the amount of crap I'm under?
I'm about to get sacked
because of the Ilsin Group story!
I know how you feel more than anyone.
But this is too random.
I couldn't find any connections
between the 11 cases he mentioned.
There's no evidence that
it was all done by one person.
Don't you think it's weird?
What is?
Hundreds of details in these cases
do not cross over at all.
That feels almost intentional.
Something's fishy here.
Even if you're right,
this is excessive coverage.
You'll get heat for crossing
the line for a scoop.
I plan to kill someone
in three days at midnight.
If you comply with the interview,
you will be given a chance
to save the hostage.
This isn't about getting a scoop.
It's about saving someone.
Drop me off here.
He may spot us if we get any closer.
Sun-ju, will you be okay?
Why are you so confident about this?
His voice.
What?
Never mind.
Please just do as I asked you to.
Could you check if 2701
is reserved under Baek Sun-ju?
Yes, ma'am.
Suite 2701 is reserved
under your name, ma'am.
Is there some construction going on?
We're replacing security cameras
due to a circuit malfunction.
- The entire hotel?
- Yes.
They'll be fixed soon,
so you don't need to worry.
I'm going to act as if
everything he said is true.
Use this for comms.
This is the key to the room
for your stakeout.
I already checked in,
so head on up from the parking lot.
And your key?
Going up.
Sun-ju, I'm in.
Install spy cams first
so that I have visuals.
I got visual and audio.
It's not too late to change your mind.
I can take over.
I can do this.
Ms. Baek Sun-ju?
Yes, are you the one who called me?
May I come in?
Yes.
Is the suite to your liking?
I chose it to my preference.
Yes, it's not bad.
A modern artist named Roth Mcwilder
designed the interior himself.
I thought it was fitting
for the interview.
Hmm...
Is this where I sit?
Yes.
I get embarrassed if you stare like that.
Why, do I look odd?
- No.
- Or...
do I look very different
from how you imagined?
No, I may sound forward,
but you look exactly how I imagined.
Is that so?
You claim to have committed 11 murders,
but not a single hair sample
was found at the scene.
You weren't captured in
any of the security cams nearby.
I thought someone so meticulous
would surely manage himself well.
That is, if what you claim is true.
Good, verify his statement first.
Are you asking me to prove
that what I said is true?
I do not like to waste my time
on a false report.
As you wish.
But you may find it unnerving to watch.
I have other videos
so please watch and check.
Sun-ju, is it real?
Give me a signal.
He's for real?
Is that enough to verify?
Yes.
We're all good then?
Am I verified?
May I start recording?
I'd like to confirm your identity
before starting the interview.
Please state your name and age.
Are you refusing to provide your identity?
It's not a refusal at all.
I just don't think that's important.
We have his face.
Go ahead with the testimony.
Okay, we'll move on.
You claim to be a serial killer
who committed 11 murders in two years.
Is this true?
Yes.
If you are being truthful,
I'm getting more curious.
Why did you request this interview?
I wanted a chance to reassess myself,
whether my actions thus far
have been justified.
Do you believe your acts of murder
are ethically justified?
Why are you asking such a question?
Because most of your victims
had criminal records,
or had generally questionable conduct.
In light of this, it seems that you
carried out vigilante acts of murder...
In the name of purging society.
Is that your conclusion?
If so, you couldn't be
any further from my intention.
I did not commit murders
with the goal of social purification.
Instead, it began with
a simple objective of therapy.
Aren't they the same thing?
The justification of healing
a sick society...
No.
It is not an abstract justification,
but a medical practice for treatment.
I'm...
a psychiatrist.
A doctor?
The people I killed...
I mean, to be precise, they're tumors.
I merely removed tumors
which inflicted wounds
on my patients' souls and treated them.
What you're saying is,
you killed those who caused
psychological harm to your patients?
You are precisely correct.
I'm even more confused now.
If it's true, more people are
tied to these cases,
why take the risk of exposing
yourself with this interview?
There are tasks in the world that must be
carried out despite inherent risks.
Am I wrong?
Then why did you agree
to this despite the inherent danger?
I concluded that it's a job
I had to perform.
And because you promised
my safety for confidentiality.
Did you maintain confidentiality?
Yes.
That's good.
I knew I made the right choice.
I knew you were the most trustworthy.
Huh.
Why the blind trust in me? On what basis?
You've been impressive
since your early years.
Sharp insight, unwavering
sense of duty, and even courage.
There is no one better than you
as my interviewer.
That's why I decided
to give you an exclusive.
It's a good opportunity for you too.
Wouldn't you agree?
No, I didn't come here with
opportunistic judgment like that.
I'm here because you blackmailed me
with a person's life.
And to save that person
you threatened to kill tonight.
To that end,
until I can confirm their identity
and their safety,
I cannot proceed with the interview.
Please tell me.
Hmm...
I don't want to.
Pardon?
I do not want to.
Let's call it off then.
I'll give you this footage.
Walk out of there. I'll take over.
If you leave now,
my hostage will die immediately.
I told you,
I wanted to give you a chance
to save a person.
In other words, you could
lead to their demise.
As soon as you walk out of this suite,
they are dead.
Does he have an accomplice?
Confirm it.
You have an accomplice?
You think my hands are tied
if I'm in here with you?
I promise you,
if you finish the interview,
I'll reveal who it is and where they are.
And give you an opportunity
to save them too.
Forget it, just come out.
Let's arrest him first.
Can I trust that promise?
Of course.
That stubbornness of hers!
Damn it!
Please keep your promise.
Absolutely.
Then I'll continue this interview.
Thank you for complying.
Catch the perp, get the exclusive,
and save the hostage.
All right, Sun-ju. Get me that promotion.
Let's proceed with questions
related to the incident.
You said your acts of murder were
intended for therapeutic purposes,
and to establish the justification,
this interview...
Wait a moment.
You're not being yourself.
Pardon?
Please proceed aggressively
and straightforward as usual.
I told you already,
I want to reassess myself
through this interview.
So assertive questioning would be
more effective, no?
Very well.
Let me rephrase that.
What was your motive
behind these gory murders?
Motive for murder...
This could be long and dull.
That's okay, we have plenty of time.
Good, I'll make it easy
for you to empathize with.
Imagine it as your own story.
There was a woman.
She was a kind woman
who lived a normal life.
She married at the age of 29,
and became pregnant the following year.
She believed that her remaining life
would be filled with happiness.
She more than deserved such a life.
But God did not grant her that wish.
Thankfully, the perp
was caught and the baby was born,
but the memory of that day
did not let her go.
It's a delusion that only exists
in your mind.
I know, doctor, but my baby's eyes...
look identical to that bastard's.
I still remember his face vividly.
His dirty seed...
spilling inside me.
She fell into the delusion
that her baby carried the rapist's blood.
No matter what, she couldn't
erase that filthy delusion.
And with the baby in her arms...
she jumped to her death.
Is this story about your wife?
I tried to be objective,
but you caught me.
Call it a psychology-led
physiological response.
No matter how much you try
to hide it, your body cannot lie.
Indeed, keen journalistic intuition.
It's my duty to filter out the lies.
Since the cat is out of the bag,
I'll speak freely.
After her death, despair was all I had.
The guilt of not being able to treat her
erased my self-esteem as a doctor.
But...
ironically, a clear purpose
in life emerged.
Revenge.
Defendant Won Il-young is
sentenced to four years in prison.
I had to wait just
four years to be able to kill him.
Due to the claim of
being mentally unstable,
the court kindly sentenced him
to only four years.
HUMAN ANATOMY
I researched every day to seek
the most agonizing revenge.
This desire for revenge
made time flow faster.
Then his release day arrived.
But as always, God did not grant my wish.
DETECTIVE KIM TAE-SIK
The day before his release,
he died from an electric shock.
The autopsy suggested a quick death,
taking only a few seconds.
It must've been anticlimactic.
"Panic state" would be
a more accurate diagnosis.
I did not have a reason to live.
No, I had a reason to die, in fact.
But as a psychiatrist,
weren't you able to find a coping method?
I did, as a psychiatrist.
I've been telling my patients,
"You must have the will
to recover on your own."
But I realized that it was all bullshit.
At least I felt much better,
knowing that I'd be joining
my family soon.
Then how did you recover from that?
I was given a second chance as a doctor.
You're the doctor, right?
Who was he?
He was an honest, hardworking man.
The head of a household
that loved his family dearly.
At least, until the incident.
Had I gone home a bit earlier...
He lost his wife
to a lunatic drunk driver.
And his 8-year-old boy ended up
in a vegetative state.
A few years later,
their paths crossed once more.
The one who destroyed his family.
He wanted to kill him right away.
But...
he couldn't do it, for his son's sake.
It's all my fault.
I felt his agony as if it was my own.
- It's all my fault.
- That agony...
I knew it all too well.
Further consultation was meaningless.
The diagnosis was made,
and the prescription was a unique one.
Did the patient agree to
this treatment you speak of?
He was taken aback at first.
"Should I..."
...kill him for you?
That's what I said.
But when he heard my story,
he felt a sense of kinship.
There's nothing more important
than that in treatment.
The trust between
a doctor and his patient.
You know what happened afterward.
So that's why.
The reason why the police were lost.
According to my research,
following the murder,
your patient was on the list of suspects.
But he had a bulletproof alibi.
Everything was...
Yes.
I planned it all.
So...
was the treatment effective?
It was perfect.
The prognosis was better
than any case I had handled before.
It was the most satisfying moment
of my professional career.
It sounds like revenge was
some kind of cure-all medicine.
As I told you about my wife,
it is almost impossible
to erase painful memories.
However, it is possible
to alleviate the pain.
And the most effective method is revenge.
Very well.
Let's get to the next question.
You mentioned feeling satisfied
through the patient's treatment,
but is that truly from
a doctor's perspective?
What do you mean?
It sounds like a killer's rationalization
from someone who has forgotten
his duty as a doctor.
Duty as a doctor...
Hmm...
I've perfectly fulfilled my mission
as a medical professional.
I practiced according to my conscience,
prioritizing my patient's health
above all else.
Was that truly the pure intention
of a medical professional?
Or were you simply
in need of a target to kill?
Yes.
How are you so sure?
Well...
I know my intentions the best.
Then are you fulfilling your duty
as a member of the press?
Pardon?
Journalists should adhere to ethics,
uphold social justice,
and prioritize the safety of citizens.
Aren't you, as a journalist,
contradicting yourself by being here?
If your priority is a citizen's safety,
you should've called the cops first.
I thought we went over that.
I only complied with this interview
when you threatened to kill...
No, no.
I'm just wondering
what your real intentions are.
It seems like you agreed to this
not to save a person's life,
but rather...
to use their life
as a means to obtain an exclusive.
Are you really here
to save a person's life?
No greed for exclusives?
I told you, I'm not interested
in any exclusives.
Good, allow me to confirm that.
Look in my eyes and answer me.
Ms. Baek Sun-ju, did you come here
to save a life regardless of an exclusive?
Yes.
I came here to save a life,
not to chase an exclusive.
Dilated pupils, trembling lips,
subtle tension on the forehead,
heart rate increased by 30%.
These are typical physiological
responses to stress.
In other words, you're lying to me.
No, I only told you the truth...
No, it's okay.
I completely understand,
so you don't need to worry.
Journalism is a cutthroat job.
Isn't that how the media operates?
Lives are at stake because of exclusives.
In such a fierce environment,
undesirable habits may arise for survival.
And without knowing how fatal
the consequences might be.
That would be room service.
I ordered some food on the way up.
Where should I put these?
Over there, please.
Where were we?
Right, habits.
Undesirable habits for survival
eventually lead to fatal outcomes.
It can make you lose your reason.
And sometimes, even a hint of greed
can lead to ruin.
Sir, it's ready.
Thank you.
Ah.
Normally, you're idle at work,
but you don't hesitate to volunteer
for suite room service calls.
Because of the temptation of a few bucks.
Am I right, Mr. Yoon Jae-sik?
What?
Do you know me?
That nasty habit of yours
has led to this fatal outcome.
I asked, do you know...
Son of a bitch! What is he doing?!
- Why did you...
- Huh?
You didn't ask why I requested
to have the interview at this hotel.
He extorted a woman for three years
after raping her and filming it.
It broke off her marriage to her fiancé.
I wanted to take care of it
while doing the interview.
Thankfully, the surgery went well.
But you said you'll kill tonight...
Yes, that's right.
I will kill again tonight.
You just have to...
focus on my future victim.
Shit, we're fucked.
Ms. Baek?
Can't do much about the dead.
You should focus on the living.
Remember our promise?
You must conduct the interview properly
in order to have a chance
to save my hostage.
You look too nervous.
Shall we change the mood?
Go on with the interview.
I'll try something on my end.
Afterwards...
I mean, after the first murder,
what did you do?
Afterwards...
Hmm...
I decided to seek out new patients.
Shit.
What am I supposed to do?
Waiting for patients at the hospital
felt like neglecting my duties.
I decided to be proactive.
How?
It was quite easy.
I volunteered at various
counseling centers.
And one by one, I found those
who desperately needed my help.
That bastard touches me every night.
- He peed on my lunch...
- It still feels like he's inside me.
- ...and told me to eat it!
- I can't breathe whenever I think of it!
He took my kidney and my family's as well!
There were plenty of people
with deep pain like my first patient.
And I began to treat them.
I always did my best.
Was the treatment effective?
Of course.
Everyone had a favorable prognosis.
The body just moved.
- He could be alive!
- It's just postmortem rigidity.
It'll stop soon, so don't worry about it.
What is it?
Do you feel a sense of guilt?
Guilt?
Was there ever a sense of guilt?
Of course not.
As I told you, I was fulfilling
my duty as a doctor...
No, not you, your patients.
A void comes after revenge.
And guilt normally fills that void.
Your patients must've felt it.
Certainly a few must have felt guilt...
There were.
What a keen observation.
Some of them expressed
distress over guilt.
Which implies that your treatment
is ultimately imperfect.
There is a distinctive reaction
to every treatment.
It is a side effect of recovery.
A doctor who addresses that flaw
is deemed genuinely patient-centric.
Are you saying you treated
their side effects too?
Yes.
How was that possible?
I'm quite proficient in hypnotherapy.
Everyone finds it unfamiliar at first.
Hypnotism is a simple
therapeutic treatment.
People typically...
live by showing only one side
of consciousness.
However, what's important is...
the flip side.
Hidden desires, instincts, and sincerities
that lie within the subconscious.
Hypnosis examines and reconstructs
the flip side of this coin.
Let me give you an example.
Do you know the composer named Paganini?
I particularly like Caprice No. 24...
One moment.
Sun-ju, can you hear me?
I'll just take care of him.
We already confirmed
that he's a serial killer,
so we have nothing to lose.
I'll enter through the door,
so just stay put.
One of my younger patients
really loved this piece.
He was a violin prodigy.
He lived with his grandmother
in a poor home,
but never lost hope.
He practiced with a cheap violin
and mastered all of Paganini's music.
But a bully in his class
was uncomfortable with his talent.
The bully harassed him for a year.
I'm outside the door.
I'm coming in. Be ready.
The bully beat him,
again,
and again...
Three.
This left hand that he used
to grab the bow...
Two.
...was destroyed.
One!
Boom!
The keycard doesn't work.
Continue with the interview for now.
Looks like you were
very immersed in the story.
Well, I have a child too.
I see...
Please continue.
What is the matter with this?
You said you have a child.
Yes.
If this patient was your child,
what would you do to the bully?
Wouldn't you want to kill them?
They shattered your child's dream.
You have to answer honestly.
You know that, right?
Yes.
Right, anyone would think that way.
Therefore, I formulated a plan
to do just that.
And I'll be carrying it out now.
What?
I'll kill them.
The bully.
What the hell is he doing?
But...
How...
Hypnosis.
I have been hypnotizing
the bully over the phone.
I first made contact by
offering a gift for taking a survey.
Then I used a keyword to control
their subconscious with every call.
Don't be surprised.
It's quite simple.
The space and an image
to focus on the hypnosis.
These two conditions are all we need.
Where in school fulfills that?
Somewhere they can focus alone.
A place where they can
bask in serene blue light.
The rooftop?
That place should be
the bully's dream space now.
Should they choose to,
they could even fly at will.
One text from me,
and they will soar into the sky.
Must you go this far?
They are still a child.
That's precisely why.
A child like that could
grow up to become a monster.
Oh, yeah.
Aren't you curious about
what happened to my patient's hand?
It was mutilated with a razor blade.
Razor blade?
To make sure it's unrecoverable...
Here...
and here.
They severed it all.
Isn't it cruel?
Shall I send that text?
Wait, wait!
Stop it.
Didn't you agree to this?
As a parent of a child?
No, I was talking about it
from an emotional aspect.
There's a long way to go before sundown.
I told you this already.
The one you can save
will be killed at night.
This one is up to me.
Stop! Stop it!
Why are you so worked up?
Could you explain your emotional state?
The bully...
Is it...
my daughter?
No, it's not.
This happened between male students.
Are you relieved?
You mentioned your daughter.
Are you experiencing
any problems with her?
Ms. Baek?
Ma'am.
Please pay close attention.
Relax as much as possible.
Do you feel relaxed?
Sun-ju, what's wrong?
Baek Sun-ju!
Can you hear me?
All right, shall we talk about it?
Is there something wrong
with your daughter?
I think she's hiding something from me.
Since when?
Six months ago.
Did something special happen back then?
A few months before that,
my ex filed a custody lawsuit.
And?
I think...
she wants to live with her dad.
Why do you think so?
Because he's more capable,
financially and otherwise.
And...
she's resembling him more and more.
Resembling her dad?
She's egotistical and selfish.
She doesn't open up to me.
I struggled so much...
raising her.
Even now...
if she knew what I put up with at work...
What is your feeling towards her now?
Do you detest her?
Be honest with me.
You do, don't you?
Am I right?
Tell me.
Do you detest her? Do you loathe her?
Mom!
What did you do to me?
Nothing.
I simply asked some questions.
It looked like you had a lot to say.
Sun-ju, can you hear me?
Have you come to?
This guy is no joke.
He'll eventually find out about our plan.
You'll have to walk out of there
on your own.
You still have what I gave you, right?
Use it to knock him out
and get out of there.
I'll take care of the rest.
Then...
Shall we continue with the...
No!
I don't think I can continue like this.
Pardon?
Please tell me who
you are planning to kill tonight.
I said I'll tell you after the interview.
I understand how exceptional
and formidable you are.
So please stop.
Why did you suddenly become so urgent?
Is there a sudden surge of desire
to save that person?
Why did your behavior change?
Tell me.
So that I can decide
whether to disclose it or not.
Okay?
Stop playing with people's lives.
Sun-ju, now. Do it!
Very well.
I'll tell you.
Please relax and sit down.
Sun-ju, why aren't you knocking him out?!
Since you're so desperate, I'll tell you.
But how effective would it be
to tell a journalist about it?
Wouldn't it be better to tell the police?
What do you...
I made an appointment
to meet a detective today.
He's been waiting downstairs
for a while now.
What's he saying?
He'll be coming up soon.
Hang on, I'll be right over.
What the hell?
Hello?
Why do you look so tense?
You can tell me.
Was there something you found unpleasant?
Or are you expecting someone?
For example...
your lover, Lt. Han Sang-woo?
Hmm. That's too bad.
He should be sound asleep by now.
Psychiatrists have incredible reflexes.
You never know when a patient
might suddenly act out.
I think you need to calm down for now.
Are you awake?
I was forced to inconvenience you.
Didn't I...
ask you nicely?
To keep...
my promise.
I... I'm sorry.
Not at all.
Since I lied to you,
I'll turn a blind eye this time.
What?
I had a different reason
for requesting this interview.
The truth is, I'm not the subject
of this interview...
you are.
There was something
I needed to check in person.
You look confused.
Why?
Are you scared?
Do you think I'll hurt you?
Is there something that burdens
your conscience?
Something that would give me
a reason to harm you?
No.
I didn't lead a bad life
for me to be someone's target.
Are you sure?
Relax and think about it again.
Is your life truly flawless?
Nothing in your heart bothers you?
Is this about...
the Ilsin Group case?
Ilsin Group?
What's that about?
Lt. Han, I think it'd be best
if you stay put.
Your actions may put Ms. Baek in danger.
Shall we continue?
What happened?
A year or so ago...
I got a call from a man named Min.
Who was that?
He was the head of
Ilsin Group's IS Bio finance team.
He wanted to blow the whistle
on his company.
About 10 years ago, an incident led to
discharging hazardous substances
into the Yeongsan River
due to lax management.
The company bribed the prosecution
and politicians to cover it up,
and he was in charge of
slush funds for this purpose.
He sounded like a just person.
It must've been a critical blow
to the company.
There was a rapid increase in pediatric
cancer rates near the discharge area.
He felt guilty about it.
Then what did you do?
I gathered evidence
through my investigation.
But...
when I was about to go to the press...
the ledger I had hidden
at home was stolen.
And that night...
Mr. Min...
died in a hit-and-run.
That must've put you in a spot.
My sole witness and evidence
disappeared instantly.
And what happened next?
The report was abandoned.
But a month ago,
my company's audit team
received a phone call.
They claimed that I colluded
with Ilsin and stole their ledger.
I told you already!
I'll do whatever it takes
to uncover the truth.
It was a tip without any evidence,
but they put more weight in
an anonymous call than my words.
It looked like they wanted me gone.
Fascinating.
Cornering an employee with a baseless tip.
A dog who lost a fight
is just a hunk of meat.
But...
are you certain about your innocence?
Perhaps you believe that someone
contracted me to kill you,
because they believe that
you colluded with a conglomerate.
Be honest.
Are you innocent?
Yes, I'm innocent.
Please think carefully before answering.
Are you really innocent?
I am.
Can you swear on your daughter's life?
Don't you dare bring her up.
I'm innocent!
Don't get so worked up.
I know very well that you're innocent.
And I know that tip was fake as well.
Because...
I made that call.
You?
Why?
To bring you here.
Think about it.
Had I not made that call,
would you be sitting here?
I did not invite you here to hurt you.
It's to treat you.
To treat me?
Yes.
Before we begin the treatment...
Lt. Han Sang-woo.
Why are you squirming like that?
It'll take forever for you to escape.
Or should I come down and help?
Sang-woo has nothing to do with this.
I planned it all!
You two must be very close.
He's an old friend.
And someone I love.
Right.
Then...
why do you think
he's so desperate to break free?
To come here and rescue you?
No, if it was for you, he should stay put.
I sternly warned him
that he could put you in danger.
The answer is simple.
The one who stole the ledger was Lt. Han.
But how...
Who knew you were
investigating Ilsin Group
and that you were hiding
their ledger at home?
Lastly, who knew you'd be
coming home late that night?
Who could this person be?
Right, there was only one person.
That's impossible.
- He's a man of integrity...
- He was.
And a very capable
violent crimes detective.
That's why he was a thorn
in the side of the syndicates.
So they laid traps.
Oh, come on.
Are you kidding me?
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
He couldn't have imagined back then.
He probably thought
it was just a coincidence.
But all of that was a carefully
crafted trap to catch Lt. Han.
Unfortunately, he foolishly took the bait.
In the end, he became a hunting dog,
sneaking investigation reports
for the criminal organization.
What a fucking moron.
Even if that's true,
why did he steal the ledger?
He had plenty of reasons.
Ilsin Group, who was tailing you,
approached Lt. Han.
They leveraged connections
with the police commissioner
to negotiate a favor
in exchange for the ledger.
In return, he wanted a promotion at HQ.
Looking forward to our future.
He thought he could demolish
the criminals who had him on a leash.
Wait. There's an inconsistency
in your story.
He never received that promotion.
He was removed from the promotion list.
You're very naive.
Do you think the conglomerates
became what they are by keeping promises?
Ilsin Group already knew
about Lt. Han's corruption.
They took the ledger and walked away.
In the end,
he became a dog chasing the wind.
Can you prove this story?
Of course.
All it takes is this little device
to reveal a man's life nowadays.
My patients are from all walks of life.
One of them is a top-tier programmer
exhausted by his CEO's tyranny.
I was able to find out
about your plan thanks to him.
So the ledger...
was taken by Han Sang-woo...
Han Sang-woo was behind the entire thing.
But what's important is that
it's not the end of the story.
This case has a witness.
You have to stay strong
as you listen to the next part.
Han snuck into your home
thinking that it'd be empty.
He ransacked the place
to make it look like a home burglary.
But an unexpected person entered.
Ye-rin was feeling unwell...
What are you doing?
...and came home early
from after-school classes.
Han needed to shut her up
in any way possible.
So he raped her.
Stop!
That's impossible.
Why would he...
She looked up to him like her own dad.
Because he knew so much about her.
He knew she didn't want to go
live with her dad no matter what.
That's why he did what he did.
If word of her rape got out,
she knew she would be taken away from you.
No, no...
It's all a lie!
How could I believe a lunatic like you?
I told you clearly.
That you should stay strong.
Then what is this?
What is this insanity?!
Call it a psycho drama.
I push patients to the extreme
to help them confront their inner selves.
I made it so that rational people
like you could react honestly
to the current situation.
What?
That waiter's victim...
works at this hotel's security team.
Thanks to her, I have access
to security cameras and locks.
You must've seen
a razor blade in Ye-rin's bag.
If you do not believe me,
ask your daughter yourself.
MY SWEETHEART
Hi, Mom.
Hi, Ye-rin. It's me.
Mom, is everything okay?
I'm okay, but...
Ye-rin, did you...
by any chance...
Mom, are you with the doctor?
I'm sorry, Mom.
I wanted to tell you but...
Hi, Ye-rin.
I'll take care of your mom,
so please head on home.
Okay?
The final choice
is the only thing that remains.
What would you like to do?
Do you wish to be treated?
Ye-rin has already made her decision.
It's all up to you now.
I want to see it for myself.
Let me talk to him face-to-face.
As you wish.
But remember one thing.
Whatever happens,
you have to believe in yourself.
Sun-ju...
- Are you okay?
- Is it true?
Did you really touch Ye-rin?
- What are you talking about?
- Tell me the truth!
Is it true?
Is it true what you did to Ye-rin?
Stop this nonsense
and let's get out of here.
Baek Sun-ju!
Are you nuts?!
Put that down!
Answer me!
Did you really hurt Ye-rin?
Sun-ju!
You don't believe me?
We have a long history,
but you'll take his word for it?
You saw him conducting a hypnotism.
He could have messed you up.
Snap out of it!
What about what she said?
I talked to her.
What if he messed with her too?
Get it together.
We have to take care of him first!
Or we're both finished!
We have to get out of here.
So calm down.
Good.
Calm down.
Easy.
But remember one thing.
Whatever happens,
you have to believe in yourself.
You think someone broke in
looking for the ledger?
Yeah.
I have to get it back.
Okay.
- Detective Lee, come here.
- Yes, sir.
Bring me footage
from all nearby security cameras.
Right, you did it.
It was you!
Stop it, Sun-ju!
Why did you do it?! Why!
It was a mistake.
What? A mistake?
I just lost myself and made a mistake.
You son of a bitch!
Stop it already!
I said stop!
You bitch!
I'm gonna kill you!
Go ahead!
Kill me!
That's enough, Mr. Han.
You crazy son of a bitch.
You're too agitated.
Shut up, asshole!
I think it'd benefit us all
to resolve this quietly.
Quietly?
Yeah, I'll resolve this quietly.
It's all over when you
and this bitch die, got that?
Please calm down.
Calm down.
Fuck you, motherfucker!
You see? You were too caught up
to see that it wasn't loaded.
Son of a bitch!
Don't worry, he's just sedated.
I'll take over from here,
so please head on home and...
please give Ye-rin a hug.
What's wrong?
Scared?
You should feel it too.
The pain and fear...
that Ye-rin must've felt.
When this bell rings, you will wake up.
How are you feeling lately?
I'm much better.
I sleep well and have no nightmares.
That's good.
By the way, doctor...
He won't ever come back, right?
The news said he went missing.
His car got swept away by a rapid,
so we won't ever see him again.
You don't need to worry anymore.
I'll see you in two weeks, okay?
Okay.
Ye-rin.
Could you ask your mom to come in?
You really do not wish to be treated?
Guilt may be tough to deal with.
I'll have to endure it,
as I've committed a crime.
And you?
Are you okay?
The blood on your hands...
won't be wiped so easily.
Ms. Kim, any more appointments today?
There aren't any more, doctor.
Then I'll head home now.
I'm feeling a bit under the weather.
But doctor...
a social worker brought in
a young child just now.
They're a victim of abuse
and wish to get counseling.
What should I do?